Finding Aid for Vice Provost for Academic and Multicultural Affairs (University of Michigan) records, 1970-2000
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- General Files
  - 1989-1997
    - Sexual Assault Prevention and Awareness Center (SAPAC), 1994 (Box 25)
    - Society for the Promotion of Indian Classical Music and Culture Amongst Youth (SPIC-MACAY) (Convention Report, 1993) (Box 25)
    - South African Initiatives Office
      - 1993-1994 (Box 25)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 25)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 25)
    - Spring Visitation, undated (Box 25)
    - Steering Committee-First Year Experience Task Force, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Strategic Data Planning: Managing the Student Relationship, 1993-1994 (Box 25)
    - Student Affairs
      - 1993-1994 (Box 25)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 25)
      - 1996-1997 (Box 25)
    - Student Issues and Problems, 1995-1996 (Box 41)
      [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2071 ]
    - Students of Color Of Rackham (SCOR), 1993-1994 (Box 25)
    - Undergraduate Experience, 1993 (Box 25)
    - Undergraduate Research Opportunity Program, 1994 (Box 25)
    - Underrepresented Minority Graduates, 1989-1993 (Box 26)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1996-1997 (Box 26)
    - Universities -- General, 1997 (Box 26)
    - University Musical Society, 1997 (Box 26)
    - University Relations
      - 1994 (Box 26)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 26)
    - Value Centered Management, 1994-1995 (Box 26)
    - Visiting Professor Nomination Forms
      - Phyllis Eileen Bardeau-Kenneth Hodge (Box 26)
      - Loretta Sweet Jemmott-Twila Perry (Box 26)
      - Lourdes Portillo-Richard Yarborough (Box 26)
    - Wade-McCree Scholarship Program, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
    - Women and Women of Color
      - "Sistahs Leading the Next Generation"-Leadership Conference, 1994 (Box 26)
      - Women-Statistics, 1993-1994 (Box 26)
      - Women of Color, 1994 (Box 26)
      - Women of Color in the Academy Project, 1994-1995 (Box 26)
      - Women of Color Task Force Workshop, 1992 (Box 26)
      - Women's Agenda, 1993-1994; 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1997-1999
    - Academic Affairs
      - Associate Provost Pamela Raymond, Correspondence
        - General, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
          [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2023 ]
        - Restricted, 1998 (Box 41)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2028 ]
      - Meetings
        - 4 + 1 Group, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
        - 5 + 1 Group
          - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 30)
          - 1998-1999 (Box 30)
        - 7 + 1 Group, 1998 (Box 30)
        - 8 + 1 Group, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 30)
      - State Budget Request, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - Academic Outreach
      - 1997-1998 (Box 30)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - Academic Policy Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - Academic Program Group, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - Academic Services Board, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - Admissions
      - Budget, 1998-1999 (Box 30)
      - Budget -- Restricted, 1998 (Box 41)
    - Ads, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - Advisory Committee on University Budgets, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - Affirmative Action
      - General, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
      - Ad Hoc Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
      - Articles
        - 1996-1997 (Box 30)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - African American Events, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - African Music, 1994-1997 (Box 30)
    - Alumni
      - Hispanic Alumni Association, 1998 (Box 30)
    - Alumni Association, 1997-1998 (Box 30)
    - American Association for Higher Education (AAHE)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 30)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 30)
    - American Council on Education
      - 1997-1998 (Box 30)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 30)
      - Fellows Program
        - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
        - Mentor Sessions, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Ann Arbor Summer Festival
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Arab Students, 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Articles, 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Arts Advisory Board
      - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Asian Americans
      - 1994-1997 (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Associate Provosts and Associate Deans Group
      - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Association of American Colleges and Universities
      - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Association for Black Professionals, Administrators, Faculty and Staff, 1997-1998 (Box 31)
    - Black Law Students Association, 1997-1998 (Box 31)
    - Budget Information
      - Expenditures
        - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
      - Unit Budget Information
        - CRLT
          - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
        - Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives
          - 1997-1998 (Box 31)
          - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
        - Office of New Student Programs, 1997-1998 (Box 31)
    - Center for Equal Opportunity (CEO) Report, 1998 (Box 31)
    - Center for the Education of Women (CEW), 1997-1998 (Box 31)
    - Century Fund for Diversity, 1997-1998 (Box 31)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Comprehensive Studies Program, 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Conferences
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 31)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 31)
    - Correspondence
      - 1997 (Box 31)
      - 1998, 3 folders (Box 32)
    - Detroit Area Pre-College Engineering Program (DAPCEP), 1998-1999
    - Development
      - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Director of Student Administration Core Process Unit, 1999 (Box 41)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2029 ]
    - Diversity
      - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 32)
      - Outside of U-M, 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Division of Research Development and Administration, 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - English Composition Board
      - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Enrollment
      - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
      - 1998-1999
        - General (Box 32)
        - General (restricted) (Box 41)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2074 ]
      - Enrollment Working Group
        - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
        - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Events Office
      - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Data, 1997-1998 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Handbook, 1997-1998 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Hiring Initiatives Share
      - 1997-1998 (Box 32)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Issues
      - General, 1998-1999 (Box 41)
      - Atkins, Keletso E., 1997-1998 (Box 41)
      - Zafar, Rafia, 1997-1998 (Box 41)
    - Faculty of Color
      - 1994-1996
        - General (Box 32)
        - Restricted (Box 41)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2026 ]
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 41)
      - 1998-1999
        - General (Box 32)
        - Restricted, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Faculty Promotion and Tenure by Race and Gender, 1997-1998 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Promotion Tables, 1995-1996 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Faculty Retention and Recruitment, 1994-1995 (Box 32)
    - Financial Aid, Office of, 1998-1999 (Box 32)
    - Financial Operations, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Foundations
      - General, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
      - Ford Foundation, 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - Kellogg Foundation, 1994 (Box 33)
    - Freedom of Information
      - 1995 (Box 41)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2095 ]
      - 1998-1999 (Box 41)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2099 ]
    - General Counsel
      - 1997-1998 (Box 41)
        [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2098 ]
      - 1998-1999 (Box 41)
    - Government Relations, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Graduation Report
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Grievances, 1997-1998 (Box 41)
    - Hispanic
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999
    - Hispanic Association of Colleges and Universities
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Hispanic Outlook in Higher Education Survey, 1996-1998 (Box 33)
    - Housing, University Housing Department, 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - Human Resources and Affirmative Action
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Indian American Students
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Indiana University, 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - Information Technology Division (ITD), 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - Institute for Research on Women and Gender, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Institute for Social Research, 1997-1998 (Box 41)
    - International Institute
      - General
        - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
      - Executive Committee, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Governing Board
        - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
      - Review, 1998-1999; 2 folders (Box 33)
    - James Tatum Foundation, 1997 (Box 33)
    - Labor Studies Center, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Latino Issues, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Latino Students
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - LeaderShape, 1996-1998 (Box 33)
    - Learning Through Community Service
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
    - Lesbian and Gay Office, 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - Living-Learning Communities
      - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
      - 1998-1999, 2 folders (Box 33)
      - Booklet
        - 1997-1998 (Box 33)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 33)
      - Proposal, 1997-1998 (Box 33)
    - Long Distance Learning Task Force, 1998 (Box 34)
    - Metropolitan Detroit Alliance for Minority Participation, 1997 (Box 34)
    - Michigan Journalism Fellows Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
    - Michigan Student Assembly, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
    - Michigan Union, undated (Box 34)
    - Middle Passage, 1998 (Box 34)
    - Midwest Consortium for Latino Research, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
    - Minority Data Requests
      - 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - MLK
      - 1997-1999 (Box 34)
    - Museum of Art, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
    - Muslim Students, 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - M-Pathways
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - National African American Parent Involvement Day, 1997 (Box 34)
    - National Alliance of Black School Educators
      - 1996-1998 (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - National Football League Education Advisory Board, 1996 (Box 34)
    - Native Americans
      - 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - News and Information, 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - Papers, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
    - Patterson Institute
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
      - Advisory Board, 1996-1997 (Box 34)
    - Penn State Conference, 1996-1997 (Box 34)
    - Population Studies, 1997 (Box 34)
    - President, Office of
      - 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 34)
    - President's Council, State Universities of Michigan, International Project, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
    - President's Initiative Fund, 1996-1999 (Box 34)
    - President's Initiative on Race, 1998 (Box 34)
    - Proposals, 1997-1998; 2 folders (Box 34)
    - Provost's Office
      - General, 1997-1998 (Box 34)
      - Tracking
        - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 35)
        - 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Racial Issues, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Racism -- U-M Articles, 1987-1991; 3 folders (Box 35)
    - Recruitment and Retention
      - 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box 35)
      - 1998-1999
        - General (Box 35)
        - Restricted (Box 35)
    - Regents, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Registrar, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Research, Vice President for
      - 1997-1998 (Box 35)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 35)
      - Wiesner Symposium, 1997 (Box 35)
      - Year of the Humanities, 1996 (Box 35)
    - Research-General, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Resumes, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Rose Bowl Reception, 1998 (Box 35)
    - Rose (Fiona) Dinner, 1998 (Box 35)
    - Seminar on Affirmative Action, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA), 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Share, New Lines, Dual Career Programs, 1997 (Box 35)
    - Sierra Leone Trilogy, 1997 (Box 35)
    - South Africa
      - 1997-1998 (Box 35)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - South African Initiatives Office
      - 1997-1998 (Box 35)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - State of Michigan, 1996-1998 (Box 35)
    - Steering Committee-First Year Experience Task Force, 1994-1995; 2 folders (Box 35)
    - Strategic Data Planning: Managing the Student Relationship, 1993-1994 (Box 35)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for
      - 1997-1998 (Box 35)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Student Issues and Problems
      - General
        - 1997-1998 (Box 41)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2073 ]
        - 1998-1999 (Box 41)
        - Individual Student Files, 1993-1996 (Box 41)
    - Students
      - Gay and Lesbian, 1996 (Box 35)
      - Latino, 1995-1997 (Box 35)
    - Telecommunications, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Thurnau Professors, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Town-Gown, 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - Trotter House, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Truman Scholarship Competition, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - United Negro College Fund
      - 1997-1998 (Box 35)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 35)
    - University Library, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - University Musical Society, 1997-1998 (Box 35)
    - Universities -- General, 1998 (Box 35)
    - University Relations, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
    - Visitors
      - General, 1997-1998 (Box 36)
      - Gwen Dungy, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Washtenaw Community College Partnership, 1997 (Box 36)
    - Whatley Proposal (re: "Fresh_Online"), 1998 (Box 36)
    - Women of Color
      - 1996-1997 (Box 36)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Women of Color Task Force, 1998 (Box 36)
    - Women's Agenda, 1994-1996 (Box 36)
    - YoHA (Year of Humanities and Arts)
      - 1997-1998 (Box 36)
      - 1998-1999 (Box 36)
    - Young Educators Society, 1988 (Box 36)
- Administrative Files
  - (Office of Minority Affairs), 1984-1992
    - General and Informational Materials (includes history of OMA), 1987-1992 (Box 10)
    - Activities Reports, 1987-1991; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Budget and Funding, 1986/87-1991/92; 6 folders (Box 10)
    - Committees
      - Advisory Committee, Office of Minority Affairs, 1987-1991; 6 folders (Box 10)
      - Publications Advisory Board, 1988-1991 (Box 10)
      - Recruiters, Committee of
        - General, 1988-1992 (Box 11)
        - Chicago Minority Recruitment Symposium, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
      - Study of Racial, Ethnic, and Diversity Attitudes of Freshpersons, Advisory Committee to 1990 (Box 11)
    - Computers, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
    - Director Search, 1989; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Electronic Mail, 1989 (Box 11)
    - Newsletter Beyond Diversity (planning materials), 1988-1990 (Box 11)
    - Staff
      - General
        - Open, 1984-1992 (Box 11)
        - Restricted, 1984-1992 (Box 12)
      - Matlock, John (memoranda from), 1989 (Box 11)
      - Meetings, 1987; 1988; 1990 (Box 11)
      - Moody, Charles D., Sr.
        - Daily Calendar, 1987-1988; 2 folders (Box 11)
        - Writings, 1985-1989 (Box 11)
  - 1992-1997
    - Activity Tracking, 1995-1996 (Box 28)
    - Advanced Planning Committee, 1994 (Box 28)
    - Advisory Committee
      - General, 1992-1993 (Box 28)
      - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 28)
      - Meetings, 1991-1993; 2 folders (Box 28)
      - Report, 1990-1991 (Box 28)
    - Annual Reports, 1993-1995 (Box 28)
    - Brochure, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
    - Budget Information
      - General, 1991-1995 (Box 28)
      - Audit response, 1993 (Box 28)
      - Requests, 1994-1995 (Box 28)
      - Unit Budget Information
        - General, 1995-1997 (Box 28)
        - CRLT
          - 1996-1997 (Box 28)
        - Office of Academic Multicultural Initiatives
          - 1996-1997 (Box 28)
        - ROTC
          - Air Force, 1996-1997 (Box 28)
          - Army, 1996-1997 (Box 28)
          - Navy, 1996-1997 (Box 28)
    - Distinguished Scholars and Artists Program, 1993 (Box 28)
    - Faculty Reception, 1995-1996 (Box 28)
    - Freedom of Information Act Requests, 1995-1996 (Box 28)
    - Institutional Contacts, circa 1994 (Box 28)
    - Minority Information Requests, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 28)
    - Mission Statement, 1993-1995 (Box 28)
    - Organizational Charts, 1995-1996; undated (Box 28)
    - Personnel
      - General, 1993-1997 (Box 42)
      - Jacina Davis (Box 28)
      - Lester P. Monts
        - Articles
          - Perspectives on Social Issues Article, 1996 (Box 28)
          - Michigan Parent Article, 1994 (Box 28)
        - Correspondence
          - General, 1993-1996; 3 folders (Box 28)
          - Personal, 1994-1996 (Box 28)
          - University of California Santa Barbara, 1993-1995 (Box 28)
          - Vice President for Research, 1994-1997 (Box 28)
        - Mentorship, 1995-1996 (Box 29)
        - Music, 1994-1997 (Box 29)
        - Presentations
          - General
            - 1995 (Box 29)
            - 1996 (Box 29)
          - American Association of Colleges and Universities, 1997 (Box 29)
          - American Association of Dental Schools, 1995 (Box 29)
          - Business and Finance Management Institute Presentation, 1993 (Box 29)
        - Travel
          - General, 1993-1997; 3 folders (Box 29)
          - American Association for Higher Education Conference, 1995 (Box 29)
          - South Africa Trip, 1997; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Project Proposals, 1994; 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box 29)
- Chronological Files, 1988-1996
  - January 1988-December 1989, 24 folders (Box 11)
  - February-June 1991, 5 folders (Box 11)
  - 1992, 14 folders (Box 15)
  - 1993, 16 folders (Box 15)
  - 1994, 12 folders (Box 40)
  - 1995, 12 folders (Box 40)
  - 1996, 12 folders (Box 40)
- Photographs
  - King/Chavez/Parks, 1988; color (Box 14)
- Minority Initiatives, 1990-1993
  - Approved, 1990-1991
    - Arizona State University Hispanic Resource -- Baker-Mandela Center (Box 16)
    - Biology Department -- Film Video Studies (Box 16)
    - Free China Student Association -- Institute for Social Research (Box 16)
    - Intergroup Relations and Conflict, Program on (Box 16)
    - Kappa Alpha Psi -- Palestine Solidarity Committee (Box 16)
    - Political Scientists of Color to Socially Active Latino Student Association (Box 16)
    - Student National Medical Association -- Women of Color Task Force (Box 16)
  - Canceled and Denied, 1990-1991; 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Approved, 1991-1992
    - Africenergy '92-Asian American Budget Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 16)
    - Association of Black Journalists Black Student Monthly-Black Law Students Alliance Butch Carpenter Dinner (Box 16)
    - Black Law Students Alliance "Evolution Malcolm X"-Chemistry Department Chem Tutor Project (Box 16)
    - Clifton Flowers New England Literature Program-Center for Middle East and North African Studies (Box 16)
    - Department of Anthropology visit by Gerald Vizenor Victor Masayesua-Department of Chemistry Scholarly Research for Urban Minority High School Students (Box 16)
    - Department of Communications Black History Month Film Series-Rackham School of Graduate Studies Summer Program for Minority Students (Box 16)
    - ICPSR Pilot Program History of Black Colleges-Minority Student Nurses Association Washington Internship (Box 16)
    - NAACP National Convention-School of Dentistry Bernard Machen (Box 16)
    - School of Music Ann Brown Visit-School of Natural Resources Teleconference (Box 16)
    - School of Nursing Funding Staff Position-Study Abroad Nicholas Ladynski (Box 16)
    - Theater and Drama "Les Blancs"-U of M Law School Symposium on Race, Poverty and Environment (Box 16)
    - U of M Library Personnel Minority Training Program-Youth Entrepreneurial Development Center Group Youth Visits/Planning (Box 16)
  - Canceled and Declined, 1991-1992; 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Approved, 1992-1993
    - MLK Jr. Day Health Sciences Planning Committee Faye Wattleton-Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority, Inc. Ball Book, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Fraternity Spirituality-Basement Arts The Colored Museum (Box 17)
    - Battle, Juan The Invisible Black Family-Burns, Patricia Coleman National Council for Black Studies Conference, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Business School Students Government MBA Corps to Africa-Department of Chemistry Graduate Student Recruiting Travel (Box 17)
    - Chemistry Department (B. Jo) Program in Scholarly Research for Minority-Dept. of Chemistry Scholarly Research for Urban Minority High School Students (Box 17)
    - Department of Chemistry visit: Professor Mjojo-Ellison-Afro American Studies (Box 17)
    - English Department Krystal A. Hall-Institute of Public Policy Women in Politics and Policy (Box 17)
    - Jackson, David Aspen Music Festival-Kyle Marrero and Timothy Jones Study Abroad at the Goethe Institute (Box 17)
    - Robert E. Megginson AISES Conference-Native American Student Association Twenty-First Annual Ann Arbor Pow Wow (Box 17)
    - New Foundation Sister Souljah "From Chaos to Clarity"-Perry, Lynn Maria Twenty-Third International Management Symposium (Box 17)
    - Phillips, Ingrid (NAFEO Conference)-Rackham School of Graduate Studies Sixth National Conference (Box 17)
    - Rackham School of Graduate Studies SROP-School of Social Work Jacqueline Mattis (Box 17)
    - Socially Active Latino Student Association, Various Activities-SPIC-MACAY Indian Classical Dance and Flute Recital (Box 17)
    - Jim Standifer Study Day on Porgy and Bess-UMAASC Budget, 1992-1993 (Box 17)
    - U of M Medical School Medstart-Zeta Phi Beta, Inc. Finer Womanhood Reception (Box 17)
  - Canceled and Declined, 1992-1993; 2 folders (Box 17)
- Mandate Encouraging Transfer Agreement (META), 1987-1994
  - Community College Advisory Council
    - Agendas, 1991-1993 (Box 17)
    - Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 17)
  - Community College Sub-Group, Agendas and Minutes, 1992 (Box 17)
  - Conference Agendas, 1988-1993 (Box 17)
  - Contract, 1993 (Box 17)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 17)
  - Curriculum Addendums, ca., 1990 (Box 17)
  - Financial Information, 1988-1993 (Box 17)
  - Goals and Objectives, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Photographs, circa 1992; 6 envelopes black and white photographs (Box 18)
  - Transfer Statistics, 1988-1993 (Box 18)
- MLK Day Symposium, 1988-1995
  - Activities, 1990-1992 (Box 18)
  - Alhaji Papa Bunka Susso, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Articles and Clippings, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Biographies, 1991-1993 (Box 18)
  - Coordinator, Michael Jones-Coleman, 1993-1996 (Box 18)
  - Confirmation Letters, 1991-1992 (Box 18)
  - Contracts, 1992-1994 (Box 18)
  - Criticism, undated (Box 18)
  - Dream Keeper Award Recipients and Articles
    - 1988-1990 (Box 18)
    - 1991-1993 (Box 18)
  - Final Report and Correspondence, 1993 (Box 18)
  - General Correspondence
    - 1991-January 1993 (Box 18)
    - June 1993-November 1993 (Box 18)
    - December 1993-September 1994 (Box 18)
  - General Financial, 1988-1993 (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Planning Committee
    - Agendas, 1990-1994 (Box 18)
    - Minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 18)
  - Press Releases, Articles, 1992-1994 (Box 18)
  - Responses, 1988-1992 (Box 18)
  - Script for Video (Box 18)
  - Speeches (Box 18)
  - "Talking About the Right Things,", 1989-1990 (Box 18)
- Office Of Academic Multicultural Initiatives, 1987-1997
  - Associate Director Search, 1995 (Box 18)
  - Attrition Study Report, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Budget
    - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - General
      - 1991-1993 (Box 18)
      - 1993-1997 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Council on Continuous Improvement, 1993-1994 (Box 18)
  - Deans' Year-end Review on Multiculturalism and Diversity, 1993 (Box 19)
  - Development, 1988-1993 (Box 19)
  - Director's Files, 1992-1994; 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Diversity Initiatives, 1990-1991 (Box 19)